Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Williamson - Retirement, 1973 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - James L. Williams, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Maude Wilkinson, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Garnet C. Wilkinson School. Pomeroy and Erie STS S.E, 1973 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Whittier School Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Whittier School, 1972-1976 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Wilmer Cutler and Pickernns Powers of the Board of Education, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Wilmer Cutler and Pickering Report on Fort Lincoln, 1978 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Wilson High School, 1975-1977 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - J.O. Wilson School, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Women Child Care Hew Conference, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Woodson Junior Senior High School Adult Program, 1973-1976 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Memos to Woodson, 1972 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Youth Orchestra Program8/1/74 (Folder 1 of 4), 1984-1989 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Youth Orchestra Program8/1/74 (Folder 2 of 4), 1976-1983 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Youth Orchestra Program8/1/74 (Folder 3 of 4), 1974 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Youth Orchestra Program8/1/74 (Folder 4 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Youth Commission Youth Opportunity Services, 1972-1976 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Youth Chorale, 1974 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Youth Alternatives (Trainer), 1972-1977 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Year Round Schools, 1972 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Woodward Foundation, 1975 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Youth Orchestra Program July 1974-July 3 1974 (Folder 1 of 2), 1965-1974 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Youth Orchestra Program July 1974-July 3 1974 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Youth Orchestra Program from Jan 1974 - June 1974 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1970-1972 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1972-1973 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1972-1973 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1964-1971 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1972-1973 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1962-1972 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Youth Orchestra Program II, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1973-1974 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1973-1974 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1974-1975 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1975-1977 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1968-1972 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Youth Orchestra Program III, 1979-1980 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Youth Orchestra Program IV, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Youth Orchestra Program IV, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Youth Orchestra Program IV, 1973-1977 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Youth Orchestra Program IV, 1970-1976 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - The Children's Foundation The School Lunch Bag (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - The Children's Foundation The School Lunch Bag (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Theodore Roosevelt High School Handbook "The Pursuit of Excellence in All Aspects of Schools Work, Undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Department of Business Adminstration Operating Procedures Manual, Undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Program Budget Supplementary Information (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Program Budget Supplementary Information (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - School Attendance Area Boundaries A Narrative of Geographical Description (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - School Attendance Area Boundaries A Narrative of Geographical Description (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - FY 1977 Budget, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Interdisciplenary Cooperative Education Programs 1976 - Curriculum Guide (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - DC Public Schools FY 1974 Budget Support Materials, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - DC Public Schools Justification for the 1974 Budget, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Federal Grant Supplement FY 74, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Capital improvements Program - 1978-1983 Instructions, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia - 1976-1981 Captial Improvements Program, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Supporting Information FY 1973 Budget, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - An Evaluation of the Model School Division Preschool Program - 1973-74, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Handicap Children, Undated (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Cuno H. Randolph Elementary School Accentuate the Positive in Education for 77', 1977 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Cuno H. Randolph Elementary School Handbook For Teachers Suggestions and Instructional Leadership, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Urban Service Cops. Current Status of Programs: September 1967 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Art Education: A Step Towards Individual Fulfilment, 1966 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Need Money for Education? Look into Basic Grants, Undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Use a Survey to Fight Poverty, 1967 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - A WTOP Editorial: President's Economical Programs, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Child Development Study Charles P. Smith, 1966 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Guideline for Teacher Education observer Participants in Early Childhood Conference, Undated (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - All Souls Church Unitarian - 1970-1971 Directory (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - An Approach to the Development of History and Social Studies Curriculum Materials, 1966 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - School Board Newsletters, 1974-1976 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Handbook for South Carolina School Board Members, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - You Want to be a School Board Member?, Undated (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Educational Materials from the People's Business Commission, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Vocational Education, 1973 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Career Couseling and Placement Services Descriptive Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Record House - 1976 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - 1977 DC State Plan for Vocational Education Part II Annual and Long Range (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - A State Plan for the Administration of Vocational Education under the Vocational Education Amendments of, 1968 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - The State of Black America, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - A Church and Care Center Greater Friendship Missionary Baptist Church, Undated (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Quality of Life 2000 and Fisk, Undated (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - The Communicator, Undated (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - SEDFRE Annual Meeting and Catalog Materials, 1971-1974 (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - Design for National Longitudinal Study of School Desegregation: Vol. 11 Research Design and Procedures, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Teaching the Decades: A Humanities Approach to American Civilization, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 27)
  - Design for a National Longitudinal Study of School Desegregation Executive Summary, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 28)
  - Thematic Units in Teaching English and the Humanities, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Guide to the Columbus Public Schools, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 30)
  - Comparison of Selected Opinions of Teachers and Aids Participating in the Career Opportuntiies Program, 1975 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Special Anaylsis Budget of the United States Government Fiscal Year 1976, Undated (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - FY 1978 General Fund Proposal Operating Budget - 1976 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - FY 1978 General Fund Proposed Operating Budget Summary Reports, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - FY 1978 Operating and Capital Budgets Congressional Submission, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Federal Grant Supplement for FY 1977 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Style Manual: A Reference For School Personnel, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Schools People and Money: the Need for Educational Reform Final Report, 1972 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - The Council of the Great City Schools, 1972 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - NYCLU Student Rights Porject Report on the First Two Years - 1970-1972 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Serendipity, Undated (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Roots: A Collection of Poetry - 1975-1976, Undated (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Literary Arts and Media Program, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Celebrate 76 - photographs by students of DC Public Schools, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - DC. City Coucil A Profile, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Iterhigh Connection - School Outlet for Student Created Products, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Alpha and the Robotmen, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - District Schools vs Suburban Schools, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - A Collection of Oral Histories, Undated (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - The Lemuel A Penn Career Center, Undated (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - 1310 Urban Journalism Workshop Vol.1 no. 1, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Aw Shoot - photographs by students of D.C public schools, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Shoes, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Literary Arts Program Book, Undated (Box 158, Folder 24)
  - Quarterly Report Project No. V 361-054, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 25)
  - Fourth Annual Report, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 26)
  - Freedom Hast Charms to Sooth Harried Students, 1975 (Box 158, Folder 27)
  - Literary Arts Program, 1975 (Box 158, Folder 28)
  - 1310 Urban Journalism Workshop Vol. III no. 2, Undated (Box 158, Folder 29)
  - 1310 Urban Journalism Workshop Vol.1 no. 1, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 30)
  - FY 1973 Budget General Information (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Tentative A Curriculum Guide in Health Education Drug Education through An Understanding of Self, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Departments of Research and Evaluation Tiltle III - ESEA Evaluation Final Report, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Departments of Research and Evaluation Title III - ESEA Evaluation Interim Report, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - English for the Seventies (1 of 4), 1971 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - English for the Seventies (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - English for the Seventies (3 of 4), 1971 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - English for the Seventies (4 of 4), 1971 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Dunbar High School 1870-1974 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Freedom Hast Charms to Soothe Harried Students, 1975 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Literary Arts Program, 1976 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Literary Arts Program, Undated (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Effective School Program, Undated (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Basic Program Information, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Announcement of A New Competition for Experimental Schools, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Evaluating Mrs. A Survey of Research on the More Effective Schools Plan, Undated (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Rethinking the Community of Teacher Corps, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Continuation of a Comprehensive Study of the Teacher Cords: Phase III Proposal to the Ford Foundation, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Technical Assistance Projects and Program Development, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Paper Criterion Levels, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - The Washington Memo: About Differentiated Staffing and Trojan Horses, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - The Micro- Social Pre-School Learning System, Undated (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Performance Based Teacher Certification: What is it and Why do We Need it?, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Levels of Community Involvement, Undated (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Regent - Relevant and Sporadically Revolutionary, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Individually Guided Education: Multiunit Elementary School, Undated (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Individually Prescribed Instruction, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 27)
  - Lexington Public Schools Bridge School Guidelines for Parents, 1969 (Box 159, Folder 28)
  - Overcoming Pittfalls in Team Teaching, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 29)
  - Interaction Briefs: Team Learning, 1969 (Box 159, Folder 30)
  - The Bridge School "Dr. Goodridge Meets and Irate Parent", 1966 (Box 159, Folder 31)
  - Team Teaching: The Danger and the Promise, Undated (Box 159, Folder 32)
  - Team Teaching: An Assessment, 1961 (Box 159, Folder 33)
  - Toledo Public Schools Bibliography, Undated (Box 159, Folder 34)
  - Team Teaching, Undated (Box 159, Folder 35)
  - 1973 Elementary School Budget Instructions (Box 159, Folder 36)
  - 1973 Budget Instructions Secondary Schools (Box 159, Folder 37)
  - 1973 Budget Instructions Central Office (Box 159, Folder 38)
  - In the Interest of Educational Services to the People of the District of Columbia, Undated (Box 159, Folder 39)
  - Summary of the Proposed Operating Budget, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 40)
  - Department of Federal Programs Presents Profiles of Outstading Projects, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 41)
  - Temple-Philadelphia Portal School Concept - 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Racial and Ethnic in Test Construction, Undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - DC State Plan for Vocational Education, 1976 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - DC State Plan for Vocational Education 1976 Part II, Undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - State Plan for Vocational Education in DC - 1975 Part II, Undated (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Playbill Bort Theatre Sarafina, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - The Inter-High Connection, 1976 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Kids Stuff - Literary Arts Program, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Lemuel A. Penn Career Center, Undated (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - 1310 Urban Journalism Workshop Vol III. No. 2, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - D.C Schools' Student Survey 1974-75, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report - Evaluation of ESEA Title I Program, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation of the ESEA Title I Program of the Public Schools of DC - 1973-1974 Final Report (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of the ESEA Title I Program o fthe Public Schools of DC - 1973-1974 Final Report (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - District of Columbia Model Cities Program Quarterly Report April-June 1972 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Bell Vocats - 1973 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Ramblers - 1973 Rabaut Junior High School (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Images Paul Jr. High School, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Ttile I Comprehensive Program - Fiscal Year 1974, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Development Skills for the Severely and Profoundly Retarded at Forest Haven, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Readers Digest; Two Against Hunger, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Home and Community Gardens Some Resource Information and a Selected Bibliopgrahy, Undated (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - The Importance of Produce in Correcting the Declining Nutritutional Status of Urban Area Residents, 1976 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Composing in the City, 1975 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Poisoned Cities and Urban Garden, 1976 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Horizon - 1974, Undated (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - The Dolphin - 1973 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Vocational Education for FY 75, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Handbook for Teachers Correspondence, 1976 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - A Program for Excellence the Organizational Schema, 1976 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Report March 1 - March 31 1974 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Title I Program Correspondence, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - A Follow-up Study of 1968/1971/1972 Graduates of the Public Schools of DC, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Career Education in the Inner City: A Career Development Exemplary Project Interdisciplinary Curriculum Grades 1 - 6, 1976 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Widening Horizons - Career Orientation Program Summer 1975 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report DC Advisory Council on Vocational Edcuation, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Interim Report 1975 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - DC Model Cities Program Quarterly Report July - September 1972 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - DC Model Cities Program Quarterly Report October -December 1971 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - DC Advisory Council on Vocational Education 5th Annual Report, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Breakfast and Nutrition, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Food Service Handbook for Satellite Schools, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Administration's Handbook on Policies and Procedures of Food Services Program, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Science Education in DC Schools A Preliminary Status Report, Undated (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Educational Resources Allocation Plan Supplement, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Better Edcuational Standards Today, Undated (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Educational Resources Allocation Plan Goal 1, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Federal Programs Committee of Education of DC, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Title I Program, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Title I Summer Proposal and Related Title I Activities, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Public Schools of DC Division of Instructional Services E.S.E.A Title I Summer School - 1974 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Summer of Acra Evaluation Team Recommendations for 1973-74 and Title Lea Actions, Undated (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - Title I Budget Supplement FY 75, 1975 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Second Annual Evaluation Report FY 1971, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - Third Annual Report - Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1971 (Box 163, Folder 22)
  - Vocational Educational and Urban Youth: A Follow-up Study, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - The National Urban Coalition, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - A Study of Comparative Data in Eight Large City School Systems FY 1974 And FY 1975 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Program for the D.C. Public Schools during the 1976 Bicentennial Year (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Two- W System of Feeder Schools Proposal February - 1973 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - A Humanistic Approach to Education through Literature, 1981 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - A Humanistic Approach to Education through Literature, 1977 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Division of Education Programs, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Division of Education Programs 1976 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - ECTC Spring Dialogue Trinity College, 1977 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Western High School See "Student Achievement", 1976 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Ward IV Proposals, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Ward IV, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Vocational Education, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Vandalism see "Discipline D.C.P.S and Law, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Union Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - US Blacks and South Africa, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Testing See "Student Achievement", 1976 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Stevens Elementary School, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Staff Evaluation, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Street Academy, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - Student Rights, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Student Achievement, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Socio-Econ and Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - Special Education, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Sizemore, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - Sex Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - Secondary Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 21)
  - School Closing (See Captial Improvements), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 22)
  - School Board, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 23)
  - School Budgets or Budgets, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 24)
  - Vincent Reed, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 25)
  - Proficiency Examination See Student Achievement IQ, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 26)
  - IQ, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 27)
  - Integrated Education:The Effects, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 28)
  - Health and Safety, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 29)
  - Gerantology, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 30)
  - Geneology, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 31)
  - Gorden Junior High School, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 32)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 33)
  - Educators, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 34)
  - Early Childhood Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 35)
  - Equalization, 1975 (Box 165, Folder 36)
  - Education and Machines, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 37)
  - Drug Abuse in Public Schools, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 38)
  - Discipline See "D.C.P.S and Law and Vandalism, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 39)
  - Desegregation, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 40)
  - D.C.P.S and Law, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 41)
  - D.C History, 1976-1977 (Box 165, Folder 42)
  - Adult Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Reunions, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 44)
  - Athletics Public Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 45)
  - Board Rules and Policies, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 46)
  - Bilingual Education, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 47)
  - Busing, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 48)
  - Capital Improvements, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 49)
  - Commentaries, 1975-1976 (Box 165, Folder 50)
  - Communication, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 51)
  - Curriculum, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 52)
  - Community Decision Making, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 53)
  - Creativity, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 54)
  - Custodial and Cafeteria Workers Sickout- Fall 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 165, Folder 55)
  - Career Ed., 1976 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Day Care, 1975-1976 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Project Head Start: A Guide for Dental Health Personnel, Undated (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Follow Through, 1973-1974 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Follow Through State Technical Assistance Grant Award, 1973 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Nichols Avenue Follow thorugh Program Funding Proposal, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Nichols Avenue Follow Through Constitution Proposal, 1974 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Nichols Avenue Follow thorugh Program Project Continuation Proposal, 1973 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Manpower Occupational Information Systems Program Department of Labor (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Manpower Occupational Information Systems Program Department of Labor (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Food Services - Summer Food Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - In School Work Experience Program CETA Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1974-1975 (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - In School Neighborhood Youth Corp, 1973-1975 (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - Model Schools Preschools, 1973-1976 (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - Berkeley Public Schools, 1971-1973 (Box 166, Folder 15)
  - Anacostia Preschool - UPO, 1973-1976 (Box 166, Folder 16)
  - Aronica Campaign, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - A Humanistic Approach to Education through Literature Spring, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 18)
  - D.C Schools Rejects Findings of Independent Study on Solving Equalization Problems, 1975 (Box 166, Folder 19)
  - Attached Critique Baratz Report, 1975 (Box 166, Folder 20)
  - Equalization- A Report on Compliance with Two Court Decisions in DC, Undated (Box 166, Folder 21)
  - Issues Concerning the Construction of an Equalization Plan for the Allocation of Schools Resources in DC, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 22)
  - Creating A Resource Allocation System for the D.C Public Schools, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 23)
  - Data Resource Book 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 24)
  - David Douglas High School, 1972-1973 (Box 166, Folder 25)
  - Court Cases, Undated (Box 166, Folder 26)
  - Creating A Resource Allocation System for the D.C Public Schools, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 27)
  - Data Resource Book 1975-1976 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between Board of Education of the City of New York and AFT, Undated (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - DC Guidance Newsletter, 1965-1967 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - A School By Schol Report System for DC Public Schools: An Outline for Action, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - For Better Public Education Inc Memo, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Summer Skills Center - 1975 Evaluation Report (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Equalization - A Report on Compliance with Two Court Decisions in the District of Columbia, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - A Quest for Equal Education Opportunity in a Major Urban School District, 1975 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - California/Connecticut/Colorado (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 168, Folder 2)